

Portfolio: thomaslongworth.com Email: thomaslong.studio@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a web developer with design focus and a strong attention to detail. Currently, I have 2 years of industry working experience in seeing projects through from planning to launch. I'm presently seeking professional opportunities inside an agency that I can learn, grow and build with.

SOCIAL

in

LinkedIn/thomaslong...



Instagram/thomaslon... Github/thomaslong...

EXPERIENCE

- Part Owner | Developer | Designer
 CedarJet Branding Solutions, Thunder Bay, ON | June, 2019 Present
 - Consult with clients to determine best possible, project specific action
 - Generate creative briefs and proposal documents for client approval
 - Create and define visual identity for branding using professional techniques(moldboards, style guides, target demographics, goals)
 - · Design and develop custom websites
 - · Design graphical content for web and print
 - · SEO and Analytics implementation
 - Web Developer Part Time

Innovated Solutions, Thunder Bay, ON | March, 2019 - Present

- Design and develop websites to client specifications in WordPress
- · Maintain, backup and secure client websites to ensure business continuity
- · Set up hosting, domains, and email for clients using WHM and cPanel
- Create graphics, animations and edit photos and videos for web and social media marketing
- · Communicate and present ideas to clients
- Front-End Developer | UX UI Design Full Time Rent Panda, Thunder Bay, ON | January, 2021 - Present
 - Perform front end customizations to rentpanda.ca(built in React.js)
 - Design visual assets for multiple media platforms
 - · Design multiple user interfaces using collaborative prototyping software

EDUCATION

Ontario Advanced Diploma | Interactive Media Development GPA - 3.8

Confederation College,

Thunder Bay, ON

September, 2018 - April, 2021

TECHNOLOGIES

- HTML 5
- CSS and Sass
- JavaScript and JS Frameworks
- PHP
- React
- C++
- Python
- Git and Github
- MySQL

- WordPress
- Drupal
- cPanel and WHM hosting
- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- After Effects
- Adobe XD
- Premier Pro
- SEO best practices

SKILLS

- Adaptability
- · Learning new things quickly
- Collaboration
- · Strong work ethic
- · Time management
- · Critical thinking
- · Handling pressure
- Team Player
- Dependability

REFERENCES

Available upon request